Guide to the Leadership Education at Duke Divinity Records, 1999-2010, undated UA.19.06.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2016-0006, 1999-2010 and undated
  - Pulpit and Pew Research Project, 1999-2005, undated
    - Forum Participants: Karen L. Wood, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Forum Participants: Dr. C Jeff Woods, 2005 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Final Reports, undated (Box 4)
  - Forum on Excellence/Advancing Pastoral Excellence (APE) Initiative, 2000-2007, undated
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, research, and reports related to the Forum on Excellence/Advancing Pastoral Excellence Initiative project.
    - Meeting Materials, 2006 May 3-5 (Box 4)
      Administrative records restricted until 2031.
    - Pre-work and Planning, 2006 May 3-5 (Box 4)
    - Lilly Planning Grant Award Letter, undated (Box 4)
    - DPLP Rebudget, 2000 (Box 4)
    - Communications, undated (Box 4)
    - Pep Narrative Reports, undated (Box 4)
    - PEP Lilly Financial Reports, undated (Box 4)
    - APE Narrative Report #1, undated (Box 4)
    - Admin Communications, Logos and Artwork, undated (Box 4)
    - Pulpit and Pew, undated (Box 4)
    - Thriving Rural Communications, undated (Box 4)
    - Admin Communications and Distribution ATL, undated (Box 4)
    - Admin Academic Graduating Class Information, 2003-2005 (Box 4)
    - Admin Research Foundations, Grants, Grant Reports and Proposals, undated (Box 5)
    - Admin Technology OIT and Office Database, undated (Box 5)
    - Admin PEP Asian American, undated (Box 5)
    - Leadership 101, undated (Box 5)
    - Mailing, undated (Box 5)
    - APE Miscellaneous Files, undated (Box 5)
    - APE Leadership 101 General Planning, 2007 (Box 5)
      Administrative records restricted until 2032.
    - Ministry and Media FTE Project, 2006 December 18-19 (Box 5)
    - APE Core Planning, Confidential, 2005-2006; 4 folders (Box 5)
    - Center/Institute Meetings, 2005 (Box 5)
    - Calling a New Generation of Pastoral Leaders, 2006 (Box 5)
    - APE (A&E) Assess and Evaluation, 2005 November 7-8 (Box 5)
    - APE: GSWPM, 2005 November 7-8 (Box 5)
    - APE: Economics Pastoral Ministries, 2005 November (Box 5)
    - APE: Core Planning Confidential, 2005 December 15-16 (Box 5)
    - APE: NWLPL, 2005 November 29-30 (Box 5)
    - APE: NWLPL, 2005 November 29-31 (Box 5)
    - APE: NWLPL - prework and planning, 2006 January 3-5 (Box 5)
    - APE: Core Planning Confidential, 2006 March 9-10 (Box 5)
    - APE: NWLPL, 2006 March 13-14 (Box 5)
    - APE: Core Planning Confidential, 2006 June 19-20 (Box 5)
    - APE (A&E) Assess and Evaluation, 2006 May 22-23 (Box 5)
    - APE Institutional Leadership, 2006 May 8-9 (Box 5)
    - APE Economics, 2006 September 26-28 (Box 5)
    - APE Economics, Prework and Planning, 2006 September 27-28 (Box 5)
    - Prework and Planning, 2006 (Box 5)
  - Duke Youth Academy, 2001-2010, undated
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, research, and reports related to the Duke Youth Academy.
    - Articles on Youth Academy and various publications, undated (Box 6)
    - Youth clippings, 2009 (Box 6)
    - Publications, 2004-2008 (Box 6)
    - DYA History, undated (Box 6)
    - DYA Lookbook, 2001-2010; 10 folders (Box 6)
    - Audiovisual CDs and Media, undated (Box 6)
  - Sustaining Pastoral Excellence Projects, 2001-2010
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, research, and reports related to the website served for articles by and about Sustaining Pastoral Excellence projects nationwide.
    - Akron Area Association of Churches, 2001-2009 (Box 7)
      Administrative records restricted until 2034.
    - American Baptist Assembly, Green Lake Conference Center, 2002-2010 (Box 7)
      Administrative records restricted until 2035.
    - American Baptist Churches USA Ministers Council, 2002-2009 (Box 7)
    - American Baptist College, 2002-2009 (Box 7)
    - American Baptist College (Continued), 2004-2009 (Box 8)
    - Arkansas Conference of the UMC, 2002-2010 (Box 8)
    - Asbury Theological Seminary, 2002-2010 (Box 8)
    - Ashland Theological Seminary, 2002-2009 (Box 8)
    - Ashland Theological Seminary (Continued), 2002-2009 (Box 9)
    - Asociacion para la Educacion Teologica Hispana (AETH), 2002-2010 (Box 9)
    - Auburn Theological Seminary, 2002-2009 (Box 9)
    - Austin Presbyterian Theological Seminary, 2002-2009 (Box 9)
    - Baptist State Convention of NC - Lake Hickory Learning Communities, 2002-2007 (Box 10)
    - Benedict Inn, 2002-2010 (Box 10)
    - Bethany Theological Seminary, 2002-2010 (Box 10)
    - Board of Church Extension Disciples of Christ, 2002-2010 (Box 10)
    - Boston University School of Theology, 2002-2010 (Box 10)
    - Capital Region Theological Center, 2008-2009 (Box 10)
    - Center for New Community, 2002-2009 (Box 10)
    - Christian Church (DOC) in Nebraska, 2008-2010 (Box 11)
    - Christian Reformed Church in North America, 2002-2010 (Box 11)
    - Church of the Apostles, 2002-2005 (Box 11)
    - Church of God Ministries, 2002-2010 (Box 11)
    - Church of God Theological Seminary, 2002-2007 (Box 11)
    - Columbia Theological Seminary, 2002-2010 (Box 11)
    - Cooperative Baptist Fellowship, 2002-2010 (Box 12)
    - Covenant Theological Seminary, 2002-2007 (Box 12)
    - Dominican House of Studies, 2002-2008 (Box 12)
    - Ecumenical Theological Seminary, 2002-2009 (Box 12)
    - Episcopal Divinity School, 2002-2009 (Box 12)
    - Evangelical Covenant Church, 2002-2010 (Box 13)
    - Foundation for the Mid South Visionary Leadership Initiative, 2002-2007 (Box 13)
    - Instituto para la Excelencia Pastoral, 2002-2010 (Box 13)
    - Lott Carey Baptist Foreign Mission Convention, 2002-2010 (Box 13)
    - Louisiana Conference of the UMC, 2002-2010 (Box 14)
    - Loyola University Chicago, 2002-2010 (Box 14)
    - MACUCC, 2002-2010 (Box 14)
    - Memphis Theological Seminary, 2002-2009 (Box 15)
    - Minnesota Conference of the UMC, 2002-2010 (Box 15)
    - NALM, 2002-2008 (Box 15)
    - Nebraska Conference, United Church of Christ, 2002-2010 (Box 15)
    - Institute for Clergy Excellence (formerly associated North Alabama Conf. of UMC), 2002-2010 (Box 16)
    - Oblate School of Theology, 2002-2010 (Box 16)
    - Presbyterian Church (USA), 2002-2010 (Box 16)
    - Princeton Theological Seminary, 2002-2010 (Box 16)
    - Reformed Church in America, 2002-2010 (Box 17)
    - Roman Catholic Diocese Tulsa, 2002-2007 (Box 17)
    - St. Francis Retreat Center, 2002-2010 (Box 17)
    - St. John's School of Theology Seminary, 2002-2010 (Box 17)
    - St. Mary's Seminary: Mantle of Elijah, 2002-2010 (Box 17)
    - St. Paul's Monastery, 2002-2009 (Box 18)
    - Samaritan Counseling Center of Albuquerque Inc., 2002-2011 (Box 18)
      Administrative records restricted until 2036.
    - Samford University, 2002-2010 (Box 18)
    - Seattle University School of Theology and Ministry, 2002-2010 (Box 18)
    - Texas Methodist Foundation, 2002-2010 (Box 18)
  - The Institute for Clergy Excellence, 2002-2010, undated
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, research, and reports related to the website for the Institute for Clergy Excellence.
    - Triangle Pastoral Counseling, 2002-2009 (Box 19)
    - Union Theological Seminary & PSCE, 2002-2010 (Box 19)
    - US Conference of Catholic Bishops, 2004 (Box 19)
    - University of Notre Dame, 2002-2010 (Box 19)
    - Upper Room Ministries, 2002-2010 (Box 19)
    - Upstate NY Synod ELCA, 2002-2007 (Box 19)
    - Wesley Theological Seminary (Lewis Center for Church Leadership), 2002-2010 (Box 20)
    - Western Theological Seminary, 2002-2010 (Box 20)
    - Westminster Seminary California, 2002-2010 (Box 20)
    - Yale University, 2002-2006 (Box 20)
    - Sustaining Pastoral Excellence Events Other, undated (Box 20)
    - Sustaining Pastoral Excellence Events - Peer Group, 2004-2006 (Box 20)
    - Sustaining Pastoral Excellence General Information, undated (Box 20)
    - Admin Programs, undated (Box 21)
    - Sustaining Pastoral Excellence Mini Grants, 2004-2008 (Box 21)
    - Sustaining Pastoral Excellence Miscellaneous Reports, undated (Box 21)
    - Sustaining Pastoral Excellence, Binders: Proposals & Program Reports, undated (Box 22)
    - Sustaining Pastoral Excellence: Proposals & Program Reports, undated (Box 23)
    - Sustaining Pastoral Excellence: Proposals & Program Reports, undated (Box 24)
    - Sustaining Pastoral Excellence: Graphic Record of meeting at Lilly Endowment, 2010 May (Box 25)